I: Hi, Ben.
B: Hi, Izzy.
How’s work?
I: It’s OK.
I’m really tired.
B: I’m sure.
What time are you finishing?
I: Well, hopefully about six.
B: Cool, do you want to meet for a pizza at Pomodora?
I can book a table.
I: Just the two of us?
B: Yeah.
Emma’s meeting some old friends from California this evening.
I: Yes! That sounds really nice.
We haven’t been out together on our own for a long time.
B: Awesome.
Let’s say seven?
I: Yeah!
B: Perfect.
See you then.
I: Great.
Can’t wait.
B: She says she can’t wait.
E: That’s cool.
B: Yep.
We’re really happy.
E: Just…be careful, Ben.
I worry about you.
B: You don’t need to worry about me.
E: Of course I do! I’m your sister.
That’s my job.
W: Are you ready to order?
B: I’m waiting for somebody.
She’s coming soon.
W: Of course.
Could I take this chair? I need it for another table.
B: Yeah, sure.